http://www.conrad.org/privacy_policy

Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy applies to websites owned and operated by EVMS (“EVMS Sites”).
Information we collect.
By using EVMS Sites to request services from EVMS (e.g. magazine or newsletter subscription, etc.) you are providing consent for EVMS to collect personally identifiable information about you such as your name, email, phone, and other information requested on electronic or other forms. In addition, we may collect information provided through social media such as Twitter, Facebook, Google, or Disqus when you log in or comment on content, as applicable. Once provided to EVMS, personally identifiable information is owned and controlled by EVMS. You may decline to share certain personally identifiable information with us, in which case we may not be able to provide you with the requested service and/or some of the features and functionality of the EVMS Sites.
Cookies or similar technologies.
EVMS Sites may utilize certain technologies, including cookies and data analytics, to collect aggregate and non-personally identifiable information about your visit to EVMS Sites. This information helps us analyze data about website traffic and helps us to improve EVMS Sites. This information cannot be used to identify you as an individual and will only be used for statistical analysis purposes.
Google, Siteimprove, Vimeo, Formstack and other third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive information from this website and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads. For more information on Google Analytics, consult their terms of use, privacy practices, and ads settings. For more information on Siteimprove, consult their privacy notice. For more information on Vimeo, consult their privacy policy and cookie policy. For more information on Formstack, consult their privacy practices. You can also opt out of the collection and use of this information through tools like the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
You can control the use of cookies through your browser settings. If you reject cookies, you may still be able to use EVMS Sites, but your ability to access or use certain features may be limited.
I consent to all cookies in accordance with the EVMS Privacy Policy.
Use of the information we collect.
The information EVMS Sites collect will be used for:
Operations/Improvements: To operate, maintain and improve the EVMS Sites and our services
Marketing/Communications: To send you marketing information about EVMS programs or services, to send you other EVMS information that we think you may find interesting, and to contact you for market research purposes.
Sharing the information we collect.
(a) Personally Identifiable Information: EVMS will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others, but may share your information with any or all of the following:
The EVMS Foundation for purposes of fundraising on behalf of EVMS. For EVMS Medical Group patients, if you do not want us to contact you for fundraising efforts, you must notify our Privacy Office.
EVMS Medical Group for purposes of following up on a patient care complaint or to improve our patient care services to you.
Service providers that provide web related services on our behalf. These service providers are contractually restricted from using or disclosing the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements.
As necessary to comply with legal requirements (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.
(b) Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain EVMS Sites. While we do not share any information that would identify you (such as email address) with third parties, they may have access to information about your device (such as IP or MAC address). We do not have access to, or control over, the technologies that these third parties may use to collect information about your interests, and the information practices of these third parties are not covered by this Privacy Policy.
Links to other websites.
Links to other websites may be provided for your convenience and information. These websites may have their own privacy statements in place. EVMS is not responsible for the content or security of linked websites or your use of such websites.
Retention, Storage, and Security.
EVMS may store your personally identifiable information for as long as your account is active or until the information is no longer needed by EVMS to fulfill the uses outlined above. Non- personally identifiable information may be stored indefinitely.
Personally identifiable information may be stored in locations outside the direct control of EVMS (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers) and EVMS may transfer information that we collect about you, including personally identifiable information, to affiliated entities, or to other third parties across borders, countries, or jurisdictions around the world. If you are located in the European Union, please note that we will not transfer information, including personal data, from EVMS to a country outside of the European Union.
EVMS is committed to ensuring that the information you provide is secure, but cannot ensure or warrant that the information you provide may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any of our industry standard physical, technical or managerial safeguards. EVMS utilizes various physical, electronic and administrative procedures including secure socket layer technology to safeguard and secure the information we collect on EVMS Sites, but no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. If you have any questions about security on EVMS Sites, you can contact as outlined in the “How to Contact Us” section below or at webmaster@evms.edu.
Access, Correction, and Deletion of Personally Identifiable Information.
We respect your privacy rights and you may update, correct, or delete any of the personally identifiable information that you provide at any time by contacting us as outlined in the “How to Contact Us” section below. At your request, we will have any reference to you deleted or blocked in our databases. Note that any personally identifiable information that you have elected to make publicly available on EVMS Sites, such as posting comments on our social media pages, will be available to others. Even if you remove information that you have made public on EVMS Sites, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of EVMS Sites, or if other users have copied or saved that information. If you have personal information that has been added to a blog, you must contact us to have any reference to you deleted or blocked in our database.
Please note that while any changes you make will be reflected in the active user database within a reasonable period of time, changes will not affect any information previously shared and we may retain all information you submit for backups, archiving, prevention of fraud and abuse, analytics, satisfaction of legal obligations, or where we otherwise reasonably believe that we have a legitimate reason to do so.
EVMS Sites are not directed toward children and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of eighteen on EVMS Sites. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a visitor under the age of eighteen on EVMS Sites, we will delete the information from our records.
How to Contact Us.
If you have questions about the personally identifiable data you have provided or if you would like to access, correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data that has been collected about you through EVMS Sites, contact webmaster@evms.edu.
EVMS complies with the laws, rules, and regulations regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data, including personal data from individuals in European Union member countries in compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation. Reports of violations of any law, rule, regulation or EVMS policy should be reported in writing to: EVMS, ATTN: Office of the General Counsel, P.O. Box 1980, Norfolk, VA 23501 or at OGC@evms.edu. Reports may also be submitted through the EVMS Ethics and Compliance Hotline at 1.800.461.9330.
